One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Government calls me a pirate who hates pirates...
But your group is a different matter.
"Hates pirates"? You do?
I suppose you would be surprised...
I spent a lot of time on Whitebeard's ship, but...
Because of my status, I had to travel underwater to get there.
I do like you guys, after all.
I seem to recall that you almost killed me once, though...
Well, you almost killed me too, didn't you?
I simply wanted to help him...
After all, Fishman Island is at peace, only because of old Whitebeard.
All pirates who travel the Grand Line pass through Fishman Island...
Shortly after the Great Pirate Era began, Fishman Island was thrown into chaos.
It was flooded with too many human pirates for us to hold back...
As well as the marines chasing after them.
Countless mermaids and fishmen were kidnapped and sold,
and just as everyone had closed their eyes against the despair...
Whitebeard appeared.
This island belongs to me now!
Those words were all it took!
After that, nobody was able to lay a hand on Fishman Island.
Such power!
I will never forget that day!
And like that he protected countless islands by claiming them as his own.
He's the pirate boss, so we can't let him fall!
What do you think would happen to the oceans if he were to die?!
The era of chaos would resume.
Anyone should be able to understand that!
The Government must have realized this too!
I wanted to stop this fight, even if it cost me my life.
I wanted to save you, Ace-san...
Jinbei... please stop.
You're being too hard on yourself...
I still haven't abandoned hope.
I have faith in miracles and chance.
Seems like things have gotten pretty interesting out there.
This sounds like a perfect chance to take down Whitebeard...
The thought of it makes my blood boil.
Why, you!
You're saying you want to take the old man's head?
I ain't the only one.
Kill Whitebeard!
That bastard's gonna die, you say?!
Now, I like that! Sounds great!
Let me out to sea!
I'll be the one to take his head!
Let me fight too!
I'll bring an end to the era of Whitebeard!
Be silent, fools!
Jinbei. Fire Fist.
Remember this well.
Try and count those who were forced to swallow their tears after being unable to beat Whitebeard or Roger...
And you'll find thousands and thousands of 'em across the sea.
That explains why we couldn't contact them...
The surveillance room on Level 2 has been crushed by the basilisk!
They beat the basilisk?!
Where are those two?!
What's going on in Level 2?!
There's someone there!
You've found them?
Yeah, but...
It seems like there are three of them now.
What?!
The Demonic Beast Floor
Rubber...
Bara Bara...
Candle...
Pistol!
Cannon!
Lock!
That giant centipede exploded!
It was made up of several puzzle scorpions!
They're poisonous!
They just keep on coming!
See, I told you so.
They were completely fooled by my "Fake Legs Master-Plan"!
You just blew our cover!
Damn it!
Oh, and I heard that the boss of the beasts in Level Two was some sort of lion-like thing...
Is it those guys?
No! Those are lions with human faces, manticores!
Guard
If they catch us, they'll eat us, even our bones!
Even our bones?!
Keys...
Please, give us the keys...
Ignore them!
They are simply able to imitate human speech because their faces are human-like!
Please, help!
It hurts... It's so painful...!
They are only imitating what they've heard the prisoners say. They don't even know what it means!
C-Creepy...
Loincloth! Loincloth!
Strawberry panties!
They're just repeating dumb stuff!
Beef steak!
Don't react!
Hey, you!
You said you'd lend us a hand, right?
Of course I did!
After all, we should combine our resources to escape from here, should we not?!
How do I get further down?
I'm headed for Level 3!
What? You don't intend to escape?!
Are you not climbing up to Level 1?!
Straw Hat plans to free his brother, Ace.
What?! Brother?!
Straw Hat, you and Fire Fist Ace are siblings?!
And you're going to rescue him?!
I'm in a hurry!
If that Ace-guy is being kept here, he must be in Level 5.
You're going to a place like that...
Stop joking around!
You must be insane!
I'm getting out of here!
Wait!
In that case, could you at least tell me where the stairs are?
The stairs...?
That's right!
The stairs to Level 1 also continue down to Level 3!
I can use Straw Hat to distract the beast guarding the stairs!
And that is where he and I will part.
Alright, Straw Hat. Let us go on together!
Leave it to me, Straw Hat!
Follow me...
There's something here...
It is the guardian of the stairs, the Sphinx!
Guard
(Man-faced feathered lion)
I-It's a lion? No, an old guy?
Omelet rice!
Beef steak!
White noodles.
W-white noodles?!
Pulled noodles!
Tan noodles!
It's learned all the noodle-types!
Pork noodles!
Handsome men!
Ikemen: Handsome man
You called?
This guy's dangerous!
Is this...?
The Sphinx is running wild off in the distance!
There's no way in hell we'd be able to escape from here!
Korean black soy noodles!
Dammit, how strong is that thing?!
Come to think of it, isn't it his fault we wound up here anyway?
I was thinking the same thing.
Right! Then, our "Escape Alliance" is hereby formed!
I sure am glad there is someone here who genuinely values freedom!
Well then, let's commence our "Straw-Hat-is-Our-Decoy-Plan"!
Hey, what're you guys doing?
H-Here it comes, Straw Hat!
Rubber Bazooka!
Why would you upset it on purpose?!
Oh crap!
You two are so unfair!
Escaping up to the high ground like that!
Pulled noodles!
You fell for it, you simple-minded creature!
That is a wax-statue I created using my candle powers!
Steamboat noodles...
It doesn't have Miss Goldenweek's brilliant coloring...
But it is quite sufficient to fool a beast such as yourself!
Which one is authentic?
Wrong!
That's so cool! It's a game of Whack-a-mole!
There he is!
Wrong!
You got it wrong. How about that one?
He's playing around with the Sphinx!
Straw Hat, how carefree can you get?!
You're in on it too, huh?
They're enjoying this more than I thought they would... Well, now's my chance!
Hey, what's up with these strange tremors?
How long are they gonna keep upsetting the Sphinx?
What?!
Can this floor even withstand all this?
This is Level 3!
We've lost contact with several monitors! We're hearing some really loud noises from above!
Mr. 3! Now's our chance!
Seems like the operation was a success!
This was nothing like what I planned!
In any case, let's run!
Is that the door to the stairs?
I'll make a key out of wax!
This is the monitoring room!
We still can't get any response from Level 2!
We have no idea what's going on!
That stupid monster!
He's caused the entire floor to crack!
This is Level 3!
A monster is falling through the ceiling!
This is bad!
Hey! That's Level 3 below us, ya know!
Sorry noodles!
Monitor room! We are at the scene on Level 2.
Can you see the image?
Yeah! Keep us updated!
Roger that!
What happened here?!
This hole is big enough for even
the Sphinx to fall through!
What does Straw Hat Luffy want?
Look! This is bad!
The prisoners on Level 2 are all
free! How did they get the keys?!
Are they responsible for this too?!
Those guards are in trouble!
Let's hear it for Captain Buggy!
He's our savior!
L-Level 2 reporting! We need backup pronto!
The prisoners are...
rioting!
Send Blugoris to Level 2!
We've just received word of Straw Hat Luffy's intent!
You did?! From whom?!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku at the Headquarters sent word!
The invader - Monkey D. Luffy and the condemned prisoner - Portgas D. Ace,
those two are brothers!
What?!
Then he came here to rescue "Fire Fist" Ace before the public execution?!
Yeah, there's no doubt!
That explains why he keeps going down!
We were focused on Whitebeard's attack!
If he pulls this off, the
tide will turn against us!
Inform Warden Magellan at once!
And get the riot on Level 2 under control!
Navy
What's so funny, Garp?!
We're standing at a crossroads that could change the world,
but he keeps causing problems one after another!
At Enies Lobby...
And the time with the Celestial Dragons...
All of this has been unprecedented!
And this time he's meddling with a prison where no-one's escaped for 20 years!
Ever since the abhorrent Golden Lion, a prison which has never been breached...
known for so long as a robust and iron-tight great fortress - Impel Down!
He has disgraced its name by being the first to penetrate its walls!
How could he be your grandson, Garp?!
He sure has accomplished a lot! I'm proud of my grandson!
Damn Bartholomew Kuma!
He said that he took care of the
Straw Hats at Sabaody Archipelago!
I knew that he was lying!
You weren't going to trust the word of a Shichibukai, were you?
Anyway I wonder how he got through the Navy's impregnable defenses...
Maybe he flew in?
Cut the crap! If you weren't known as the hero of the Navy,
I would have made you take full responsibility for your family, Garp!
You can take this old man's life but the situation is far more serious than that!
It's not funny!
This has all been the Navy's blundering!
Do you realize how much Tsuru and I worked to deal with the aftermath?!
Hey, that's mine! Give it back!
Shut up!
Hot!
Ow ow ow...
Ow ow ow! This floor is like a frying pan!
Are we in the desert?! It's so hot!
Why is it so quiet?
Level 3! Oh I never wanted to come here!
Straw Hat! I'm doomed along with you again!
Oh! Looks like the lion's taking a cat nap!
This is especially difficult for me and my wax powers.
Alright, let's just go.
Wow! Grilled chicken is served!
Don't be ridiculous!
That's a hummingbird that fluttered down from upstairs and got grilled in the air.
How hot is it in here?!
Hey, can we just get in...
Isn't it a miserable sight?
Prisoners on this floor were once all tough criminals with over 50,000,000 belly bounties.
The heat from the Burning Heat Hell underneath...
along with depriving them of food and water has made them half dead.
This is Level 3 - the Starvation Hell!
Now you know why this floor is covered with sand.
Odds are the sand beneath us
are remains of a prisoner who dried up.
If we stay here too long, we will become like them before we know it.
We have to get away from here while we still have sweat to spare.
Alright, let's hurry down to Level 4!
As if!
Hey, not that way! We gotta take the stairs on the left.
Oh yeah?
No, we should take the pass on the right.
Which one is it?!
Why...
...are we back where we started from?!
I hope we make it to Level 4 soon.
We told you, we're not going!
You have to guide me!
You said that we were gonna save Ace together!
We never said that!
Stop imagining things as you want them to be!
Didn't you say you would?
They are in!
Alright, draw the net!
Yes sir!
I'm going on my own, then!
Huh?
What's this?!
Oh no! It's a trap! They got us already!
It's made of iron!
I can't use my Bara Bara Fruit power!
Of course it contains Sea Prism Stone!
They're gonna torture us for attempting to break out.
We're goners.
The invader Straw Hat Luffy has been captured, along with two others!
What do you mean "two others?!"
Don't antagonize them Buggy-kun!
It's over.
Damn it! I gotta rip this net!
There are guards and Blugoris here!
Put the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
Roger!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Who're you?
I'm Saldeath.
Saru-desu: I'm a monkey.
Huh, really? But you don't look like one.
No!
You're not listening.
I'm Saldeath.
Huuh, really?
No! Get it right! It's my name!
Give up.
Chief Guard
Saldeath (Blugori Commander)
It's no use holding out.
There's no place to get away in this isolated underwater prison!
It's lucky you were caught by me.
Because there are four demon guards prowling around on the floors beyond this.
What?!
He's right! I don't wanna face them and the warden!
Vongole bianco!
Oh, Chief!
Soup spaghetti!
He's onto pasta now!
We're gonna get squashed!
Spaghetti!
The Sphinx is awake!
Oh no, he's gonna break the net!
Don't let those three, especially Straw Hat, get away!
Deep-fried noodles!
He's back on noodles again!
He must've been going through a phase!
Yay!
This is great! Now we can run!
Get them!
Rubber...
Gatling!
Oh? Where did those two go?
Hurry up, Mr. 3!
I can't move quickly due to this heat...
Ah! They climbed up the net!
Straw Hat!
If you see Ace tell him that I said "Hello" and
"Let's have a drink if I ever see you again alive!"
Be a good little live bait for us, stupid!
I was happy to see you were alright but... Alright! See ya!
Thanks for helping me!
Ugh! How sweet!
Ouch! It's heartbreaking!
Stay sharp! He is a pirate with a 300,000,000 belly bounty!
Now is our chance to run!
Alright!
I don't have time to fight you all!
Buckwheat noodles!
Oh no! He's still around!
You bastard!
He's gonna run! Chase him!
Where are the stairs to go down?!
It's hot...
We'll be safe here! They're after Straw Hat as we wished.
They closed up the staircase going up.
It's already too much for me to stay here.
Un deux faint!
Un deux come on!
Who's singing?
Un deux faint!
Un deux come on!
You know this world is about a man and a woman!
But when you're an okama you're a little of both!
That's why we're the greatest!
The greatest!
The okama way is the greatest!
The okama way!
The okama waaay!
You guys are doing great!
I spin and spin like I'm caught up in the tide of the times!
This way!
Wait! Listen to me! That's...
Guys! You can't be that tired!
This stifling heat is nothing!
I can be even more stifling!
Oh! If it isn't Mr. 3!
Just as I thought. It's you...
What?! Mr. 3?!
Hey wait a minute! Why're you here?!
You're behind bars so you've been caught?!
No no. The one who has been caught is me!
I was so surprised I had to do a double take with an "Okama Way" Kenpo called...
Looking Back on that Autumn Night's Dream!
Hey! What kind of creature is this?!
Let's be sure not to let him out.
What're you saying?! Let me out!
How did he slip through our tight security?!
There's just one invader.
But if Ace were to be rescued, Impel Down, as well as
the World Government, would be humiliated!
We're gonna get into that prison,
and in the name of Navy Headquarters, we must catch Straw Hat Luffy!
Wait a minute!
W-Who are you?!
I'm Sadie-chan who loves torturing people!
Impel Down
Security Chief Sadie-chan
After being breached by an intruder taking Navy help,
would only further disgrace Impel Down's name!
She can't be serious, using "chan" to refer to herself...
Shut up!
You better call me "Sadie-chan!"
I can't resist those screams!
Damn you!
Hold it! Are you saying that you don't need our help?
Yes. This prison is a labyrinthine hell.
If you don't know it well, you can't help us!
We'd appreciate your help if you just guard the outside.
We'll raise this drawbridge which is the only entrance to the prison...
...and seal off Impel Down completely!
Don't worry. There is no way out...
...of this underwater prison!
Alright, then we'll guard the outside.
Yes, that's a good boy.
A koala?
You're kidding me!
A koala.
A koala?
Impel Down is now completely sealed off!
Hannyabal?!
Magellan's here too. What's going on?
You have a special visitor, Ace!
Guess who's here!
Jinbe! Even you have never met her before,
so there's no way that Ace can guess who it is.
She's well-known but never shows herself! She leads the Kuja - the tribe of warriors!
She's one of the Royal Shichibukai!
Strong, noble, and the most beautiful woman in the world!
She is the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Yeah yeah, Hancock! Hancock-sama!
Yo, goddess! When I become warden, will you marry me?!
Please!
Ouch! I really wanna become the warden!
Ah, I got it wrong. I mean it really hurts to be hit by the warden!
What are you doing?!
Wow! For real?! She is so beautiful!
So she's the Snake Princess of the Kuja? Hey, turn around!
Hancock-chan!
Look how sexy she is!
Young lady! Come to our cell!
We will love you tenderly!
What a good smell! I wanna visit the Maiden Island!
There's only women and everybody's naked there right?
What do you want from me?
Nothing. I just wanted to take a look at you.
Because you will become the cause of the war that I will take part in.
So I'm worth a look then?
Boa Hancock! Are you ignoring us?!
Come here!
You've always been an empress with a strong will who never obeyed any summonses...
But you're taking part in this war?
Suddenly you value your title of Shichibukai?!
So you're Jinbe. Don't snarl at me.
Yo yo, young lady! Young lady!
They're talking! Shut your mouths!
Shut up Magellan, you round-the-clock diarrhea man!
Yeah, he's right!
Hey, Snake Princess!
I bet the girls on the Maiden Island are hungry for us guys!
Hey you! Give me your post as warden!
Vice Warden.
You guys!
She turned!
You keep taunting me with those coarse voices...
I'm scared!
Oh god! I can't resist!
How cute she is! Let us have her, Diarrhea Man!
This is the vilest place in the world! It makes me sick!
The prisoners call you "Diarrhea Man."
How can you stand it, Warden?
They must've crushed any pride you take in your job...
Wow! She's irresistible!
Shame on you, Diarrhea Man!
However...
Let me have her, Diarrhea Man!
Diarrhea Man! Let me have Hancock!
I'm infuriated at their rudeness!
Wha-! Warden, w-w-wait!
That's gonna harm us too! No!
You've gotten carried away!
Ugh! Oh man!
I have to show you...
who is boss in this prison!
What're you doing?!
Stop, Magellan!
You fool! We were just joking! Don't!
That bastard... He seriously did it!
T-That's it! You're gonna die!
I need... I need an antidote! Shit!
Never forget that I have the authority and the ability to execute each and every one of you at my whim!
All right, Hancock-dono. You can talk freely now.
I'm done.
Hey! Is what you just told me true?!
Why would I lie to you?
Oh yeah.
He was worried that you might get mad.
Are you done already?
What were they talking about?
Beats me. I was trying really hard to get away from you.
Ace-san.
What did she just tell you?
She said that my brother's here!
What?! The one with a straw hat that you always talk about?!
That's insane!
Ah? I didn't notice, but I'm climbing now! I wanna go down!
But I guess If I keep going, it's gonna go downwards at some point!
I'm hungry!
We got an image! He's about to enter district C!
Alright I see him!
Sea Prism Stone nets again!
That was close!
Oh no! The lion!
Damnit!
Wait a minute, lion!
I'm here to help you!
Zoro!
I fooled you!
Swan Arabesque!
Swan swan!
Oh?
Spin spin! I'm spinning!
He's not Zoro but he sounds familiar...
It's been a long time! Straw-chan, it's me!
Bon-chan!
I'm so disappointed that you're not Zoro, but at least you're alive!
It's our chance! Get Straw Hat!
Go away!
You assholes! What do you think you're doing to my friend?!
Yeah, Sphinx! Fight back!
Okay! He's not gonna attack us after getting busted up like this!
You gotta get rough to teach a wild animal a lesson!
Fried noodle bun...
Hey Bon-chan! I thought that you were dead...
after sacrificing yourself for us!
Gimme a break! Okamas never die!
Oh, is that right?!
Let's see how Mr. 2 Bon Clay's power works!
He ate the Clone Fruit and turned into a Clone Man.
He can turn into anyone whose face has been touched by his right hand.
He turned into Zoro because he touched him before.
Here's another escapee!
He keeps gaining friends as he descends deeper and deeper!
Blugoris! Don't let them get away!
By the way Straw-chan, I heard that you wanna get to Level 5!
Indeed! Can you show me the way?
Alright, I'll go with you!
Actually, there's someone that I wanna see on Level 5!
Really?!
Okay, then let's do it together!
Uh-huh!
Let's go!
Yeah!